[{
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D#_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D#add9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Em",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F#"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Fm7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "C",
        "wrongAnswer2": "B",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F#m7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F#_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "F#7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "B#7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A#m",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C#m"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G#_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G#add9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "G",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A#m7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G#_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G#m7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "F#add9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "B",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F#_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "F#add9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Fadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "G",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Cm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "C#7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "G#add9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G#_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G#m",
        "wrongAnswer1": "D7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "F#add9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "A7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C#_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C#_7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E#7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='B' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "B",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Fm7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Aadd9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "C#add9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Gadd9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Badd9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A#_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A#m",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C#' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C#",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Gm",
        "wrongAnswer2": "G#",
        "wrongAnswer3": "D#"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Dm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Cm",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Gadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Bm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Gm7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "F",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Dm",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C#"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    }
]